{
    "challengeLevels": [
      {
        "uid": 1,
        "questionText": "Is Monday a day of the week?",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Yes",
        "challengeId": 3
      },
      {
        "uid": 2,
        "questionText": "Is Tuesday a day of the week?",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Yes",
        "challengeId": 3
      },
      {
        "uid": 3,
        "questionText": "Is Wednesday a day of the week?",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Yes",
        "challengeId": 3
      },
      {
        "uid": 4,
        "questionText": "Is Thursday a day of the week?",
        "difficulty": 4,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Yes",
        "challengeId": 3
      },
      {
        "uid": 5,
        "questionText": "How many numbers are there before 10?",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "10",
        "challengeId": 4
      },
      {
        "uid": 6,
        "questionText": "What is the best type of biscuit?",
        "difficulty": 4,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Gingernuts",
        "challengeId": 5
      },
      {
        "uid": 7,
        "questionText": "What does S stand for in STEM?",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Science",
        "challengeId": 6
      },
      {
        "uid": 8,
        "questionText": "What does T stand for in STEM?",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Technology",
        "challengeId": 6
      },
      {
        "uid": 9,
        "questionText": "What does E stand for in STEM?",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Engineering",
        "challengeId": 6
      },
      {
        "uid": 10,
        "questionText": "What does M stand for in STEM?",
        "difficulty": 4,
        "answerType": 0,
        "answer": "Maths",
        "challengeId": 6
      }
      
      
    ]
  }